ph-creative.com 2008-05-14

# Liverpool 0151 708 2280, Web Design, E-marketing, Graphic Design, CMS > Privacy

|  | 

Wednesday, May 14, 2008

|   
  
---|---  
| 

---|---  
---|---  
---|---  
---|---  
---|---  
   
| | | |   
---|---|---  
|  |   
---|---  
|  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---  
| 

## Our Privacy Policy

PH-Creative.com takes your privacy seriously. Your personal information will not be sold or otherwise distributed to third parties without your consent. PH-Creative.com is not a source of unsolicited email. 

### What Our Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers what personal information PH-Creative.com collects, how that information is collected and why we need it. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not cover the practices of companies other than PH-Creative.com or people who are not employed or managed by PH-Creative.com. Third party sites provide the products and services listed on PH-Creative.com and these sites have their own privacy statements and are not covered by this policy. 

### What Information We Collect and How We Use It

Providing your email address to PH-Creative.com is optional and used solely to update you with new products and services that our site has to offer, or to respond to and queries you have sent PH-Creative.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, and the page(s) you request. This information is collected anonymously and is used to better understand how people use our site and improve its performance. 

### Who Has Access to Your Information

As a matter of policy PH-Creative.com does not sell, rent, share or otherwise distribute any of your personal information to third parties except in certain specific circumstances. Those circumstances are as follows: 

  1. We receive a subpoena, court order or other legal demand for your information. 
  2. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or as otherwise required by law. 
  3. PH-Creative.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event PH-Creative.com will notify you before your information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  4. Some of our services allow you to make certain information public or accessible to certain individuals. If you make use of these services PH-Creative.com will share your information as you request. 

### What are Cookies and Why do We Use Them

Cookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their members. Cookies allow us to store and retrieve login and other information on a user's system. They provide us with data that we can use to improve our service to you. Cookies themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. The default setting for most browsers is to accept cookies; if you prefer you can set yours to refuse them. If you choose not to accept cookies you will not be able to take full advantage of PH-Creative.com. 

### What Happens if PH-Creative.com Makes a Change to This Policy?

If PH-Creative.com intends to make a change to our privacy policy we will post a notice on this site and we will also notify you by email. 

### How You Can Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website you may get in touch with us through the Contact Us page. 

### How to Unsubscribe

If no longer wish to receive updates on the products and services that we offer then please send an email from that address with the word ‘unsubscribe’ in the subject.   
  
---  
| [[Site Map](http://www.ph-creative.com/sitemap)]  [[Privacy Policy](http://www.ph-creative.com/privacy)]  [[Terms, Conditions and Legal](http://www.ph-creative.com/legal)]   |  [](http://validator.w3.org/check?uri=referer)  
---|---
